export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How often do you find yourself incorporating DevOps practices into your development workflow?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Almost always+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you tend to share your DevOps knowledge and practices with others or prefer to keep it to yourself?",
      "options": [
        "Share with others+3",
        "Keep to myself+1",
        "Varies depending on the situation+2",
        "I'm not familiar with DevOps+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Share with others"
    },
    {
      "question": "What motivates you the most to embrace DevOps principles in your projects?",
      "options": [
        "Streamlining workflows and efficiency+1",
        "Automating deployment processes+2",
        "Enhancing collaboration between teams+3",
        "Curiosity and exploration of DevOps+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Curiosity and exploration of DevOps"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your expertise level in implementing DevOps practices?",
      "options": [
        "Beginner+0",
        "Intermediate+1",
        "Advanced+2",
        "Expert+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Intermediate"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you actively seek new methods and tools for continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) in DevOps?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, regularly+0",
        "Sometimes+1",
        "Rarely+2",
        "No, not at all+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Yes, regularly"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others sought your advice or expressed appreciation for your DevOps knowledge?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, frequently+3",
        "Occasionally+2",
        "Rarely+1",
        "No, never+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Occasionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you feel a sense of accomplishment after successfully implementing DevOps practices in a project?",
      "options": [
        "Always+0",
        "Sometimes+1",
        "Rarely+2",
        "Never+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Always"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you attended DevOps-related conferences or sought professional certifications?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+0",
        "Considering it+1",
        "No, not yet+2",
        "No, and I don't plan to+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the impact of DevOps practices on your project delivery and collaboration with teams?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact+1",
        "High impact+2",
        "Very high impact+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "High impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that adopting DevOps is essential for achieving efficient and collaborative software development?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+0",
        "Agree+1",
        "Neutral+2",
        "Disagree+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    }
  ]
}
